stylingyou.com.au 2015-10-04

# Privacy - Styling You :: Styling You

Styling You is committed to the Australian privacy legislation in the way it collects, uses, secures and discloses personal information. The Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988 requires companies to comply with the National Privacy Principles (NPPs).

We lawfully collect personal information that is necessary for our business to function. The information we collect and hold will depend upon the products and services you request from us and may include:  
Information you provide us when you purchase goods or services. This information will include your name, address and contact details.

Information derived from communications between us and you. We also collect information about you when you download content from our website www.stylingyou.com.au  
The use of the facilities and services available through our website will determine the amount and type of information we collect. The only personal information we collect when you use our website is what you tell us about yourself, for example, by joining our online community, obtaining membership to our site, participating in our forums or when you send us email we will record your mail address.

We use the information we collect for the purpose disclosed at the time of collection or otherwise as set out in this Privacy Statement. We will not use your personal information for any other purpose without first seeking your consent, unless authorised or required by law.

If you at any time receive any communication from www.stylingyou.com.au which you would not like to receive, please contact us and we will remove your name from our mailing list. If you would like to check or amend your contact details, please contact us. We will deal with all requests for access to personal information as quickly as possible.

## Stay in touch

For a daily email update, click **[HERE](http://stylingyou.us1.list-manage1.com/subscribe?u=afd8caaaa2f099e64f6a643f8&id=40ed249bb6)**. Or hit the subscribe button below for weekly news in your inbox.
